{"status":"Success","data":{"question_paper":[{"question_no":"1","question":"\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d41 1500 \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f 1320 \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41. \u0d0e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d36\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02?","option1":"10%","option2":"12%","option3":"17%","option4":"13%","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"2","question":"\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d 50% \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d23\u0d02. \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d 172 \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e 28 \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32. \u0d0e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d15\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30?","option1":"50","option2":"100","option3":"200","option4":"400","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"3","question":"2000 \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d35\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d7b 10% \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d 10% \u0d21\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u200c\u0d15\u0d57\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41. \u0d0e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d07\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d34\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d? ","option1":"2010","option2":"1800","option3":"2000","option4":"1980","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"4","question":"10 \u0d38\u0d46\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d02, 6 \u0d38\u0d46\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40 \u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d35\u0d40\u0d24\u0d3f, \u0d38\u0d46\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40 \u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d09\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d1a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d 3 \u0d38\u0d46\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40 \u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d02? ","option1":"7","option2":"4","option3":"5","option4":"6","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"5","question":"\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d48\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7e \u0d1a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 10 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d31\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e 32 \u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d26\u0d42\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41. \u0d0e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d 4 \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d26\u0d42\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d31\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d47\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d30\u0d41\u0d02?","option1":"125","option2":"12800","option3":"1250","option4":"1280","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"6","question":"\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f 5000 \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a 20% \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d7c\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d36 \u0d15\u0d23\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d47\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41. \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d46 \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02?","option1":"6050","option2":"1000","option3":"1050","option4":"6000","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"7","question":"\u0d2e\u0d42\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d36\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d30\u0d3f 12 \u0d09\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d36\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d30\u0d3f 10 \u0d09\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d36\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d30\u0d3f 14 \u0d09\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d23\u0d46\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d?","option1":"16","option2":"8","option3":"12","option4":"28","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"8","question":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d47\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? 2,7,3,26,4, ..............","option1":"5","option2":"35","option3":"63","option4":"15","answer":"63"},{"question_no":"9","question":"TEACHER\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d 205138518 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d30\u0d39\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7d STUDENT \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?","option1":"192021451420","option2":"19202145120","option3":"192021451520","option4":"192021451320","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"10","question":"\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d41\u0d15.\nTomorrow : Yesterday :: Saturday : ","option1":"Thursday","option2":"Monday","option3":"Sunday","option4":"Friday","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"11","question":"+ \u0d17\u0d41\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 x \u0d38\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d32\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u00f7 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d15\u0d32\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 - \u0d39\u0d30\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d42\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d35\u0d46\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d (18+10x20)-8\u00f76 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30?","option1":"92","option2":"19","option3":"35","option4":"26","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"12","question":"\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d02 12.30 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d42\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d42\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d42\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d33\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d21\u0d3f\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?","option1":"160","option2":"110","option3":"165","option4":"180","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"13","question":"\u0d05\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d7c \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d36\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d1a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d. A \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d24\u0d41\u0d35\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f B \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 B \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d07\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d41\u0d35\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f C \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 C \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d24\u0d41\u0d35\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f D \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 D \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d24\u0d41\u0d35\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f E \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41.","option1":"A","option2":"B","option3":"C","option4":"D","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"14","question":"2012 \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d41\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3f 1 \u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7d 2013\u0d7d \u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02","option1":"\u0d36\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d1a","option2":"\u0d35\u0d46\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d1a","option3":"\u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d1a","option4":"\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d1a","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"15","question":"A,X\u0d7b\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 X ,Y \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d02 Y, Z \u0d7b\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41. \u0d0e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d A \u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d Z \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e","option2":"\u0d2a\u0d57\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f","option3":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d7b","option4":"\u0d05\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1b\u0d7b","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"16","question":"\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d33\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f?","option1":"\u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33","option2":"\u0d38\u0d3f.\u0d0e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d. \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d2f","option3":"\u0d2a\u0d3f.\u0d15\u0d46.\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d26\u0d47\u0d35\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d7c","option4":"\u0d06\u0d7c.\u0d36\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"17","question":"'\u0d17\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35' \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d18\u0d4b\u0d37\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?","option1":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d38\u0d3f","option2":"\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d16\u0d4d ","option3":"\u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27","option4":"\u0d07\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d02","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"18","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d15\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d","option1":"\u0d21\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d41. \u0d0e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d . \u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d7c ","option2":"\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d35\u0d7d \u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d34\u0d4d\u200c\u0d38\u0d4d ","option3":"\u0d21\u0d3f. \u0d09\u0d26\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c ","option4":"\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d7a ","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"19","question":"\u0d2a\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d20\u0d28\u0d02?","option1":"\u0d13\u0d7a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d1c\u0d3f","option2":"\u0d13\u0d21\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d1c\u0d3f ","option3":"\u0d13\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f","option4":"\u0d13\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d2f ","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"20","question":"\u0d15\u0d36\u0d41\u0d35\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d17\u0d35\u0d47\u0d37\u0d23 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d28\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?","option1":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d02","option2":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d","option3":"\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d","option4":"\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d02","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"21","question":"'\u0d2a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d02' \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d?","option1":"\u0d1a\u0d4a\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35","option2":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4b","option3":"\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d38\u0d4d","option4":"\u0d36\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d7b","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"22","question":"\u0d10\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d39\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?\r\n","option1":"\u0d1c\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7b","option2":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d21","option3":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f","option4":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7b","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"23","question":"'\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4b' \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d?","option1":" \u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d","option2":"\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f","option3":"\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d7b","option4":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7b\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"24","question":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d?","option1":"\u0d28\u0d48\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d7b ","option2":"\u0d39\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d7b","option3":"\u0d13\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d7b","option4":"\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d7b","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"25","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d25\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41?","option1":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d02","option2":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02","option3":"\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 ","option4":"\u0d06\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d25","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"26","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d48\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ","option1":"\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d3f","option2":"\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32","option3":"\u0d12\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d09\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d7b","option4":"\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"27","question":"\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d35\u0d7c \u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d09\u0d7e\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41?","option1":"\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02","option2":"\u0d37\u0d21\u0d4d\u200c\u0d2a\u0d26\u0d02","option3":"\u0d09\u0d2d\u0d2f\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f","option4":"\u0d09\u0d30\u0d17\u0d02","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"28","question":"\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f?","option1":"\u0d12.\u0d0e\u0d02.\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7c","option2":"\u0d2a\u0d3f.\u0d1f\u0d3f. \u0d09\u0d37","option3":"\u0d37\u0d48\u0d28\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d7a","option4":"\u0d15\u0d46.\u0d2a\u0d3f. \u0d24\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d4d","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"29","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30 \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d?","option1":"\u0d38\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d7c 16","option2":"\u0d38\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d7c 2","option3":"\u0d12\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d7c 2","option4":"\u0d12\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d7c 16","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"30","question":"\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d1c\u0d47\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d","option1":"\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d7e\u0d2c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d","option2":"\u0d17\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d47\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d7e","option3":"\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d31\u0d3f","option4":"\u0d1c\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d06\u0d21\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d ","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"31","question":"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d47\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d15\u0d57\u0d7a\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d47\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30?","option1":"25","option2":"18","option3":"21","option4":"35","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"32","question":"2013\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d?","option1":"\u0d21\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f ","option2":" \u0d09\u0d37\u0d3e \u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d35\u0d4d","option3":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d7b","option4":"\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"33","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d28 \u0d2d\u0d47\u0d26\u0d17\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d05\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d38\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d02\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d3f","option2":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3f","option3":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f","option4":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d4d","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"34","question":"\u0d2c\u0d02\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d7e \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2d\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d?","option1":"1905","option2":"1915","option3":"1904","option4":"1906","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"35","question":"\u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30 \u0d31\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d35\u0d47\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?","option1":"\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d7c","option2":"\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d21\u0d7d\u0d39\u0d3f","option3":"\u0d05\u0d32\u0d39\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d4d","option4":"\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d48","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"36","question":"\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d31\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d09\u0d7e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d?","option1":"\u0d0e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d48\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d21\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f","option2":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f","option3":"\u0d15\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f","option4":"\u0d06\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"37","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24 \u0d2d\u0d42\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d17\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d7c \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d31\u0d7d?","option1":"\u0d21\u0d7d\u0d39\u0d57\u0d38\u0d3f","option2":"\u0d35\u0d46\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f","option3":"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d7a\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d","option4":"\u0d15\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d7a \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2d\u0d41","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"38","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d46\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d05\u0d02\u0d17\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d02?","option1":"292","option2":"285","option3":"385","option4":"395","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"39","question":"1953 \u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d28\u0d38\u0d02\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d37\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d02\u0d17\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ","option1":"\u0d38\u0d7c\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d15\u0d46. \u0d0e\u0d02. \u0d2a\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c","option2":"\u0d38\u0d3f. \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f","option3":"\u0d39\u0d43\u0d26\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d25\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d41\u0d7a\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d41","option4":"\u0d1c\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d38\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d32\u0d3f","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"40","question":"\r\n\u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d23\u0d35 \u0d35\u0d48\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d09\u0d7d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46?","option1":"\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d","option2":"\u0d38\u0d42\u0d31\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d ","option3":"\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d46","option4":"\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d42\u0d7c","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"41","question":"\u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 5 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d 11 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d35\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41?","option1":"\u0d2e\u0d57\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e","option2":"\u0d2a\u0d57\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d","option3":"\u0d2e\u0d57\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d7e","option4":"\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d15 \u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"42","question":"\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?","option1":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48 ","option2":"\u0d21\u0d7d\u0d39\u0d3f ","option3":"\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d48","option4":"\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d42\u0d7c ","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"43","question":"\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d2a\u0d40\u0d21\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d7e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d?","option1":"2000","option2":"2002","option3":"2005","option4":"2010","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"44","question":"\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d37\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \ufffd\ufffd \u0d36\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d36\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d you \u0d1c\u0d3f \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d40\u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d?","option1":"\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d23 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7c","option2":"\u0d21\u0d3f. \u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d. \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f ","option3":"\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d7a \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d1c\u0d7b\u0d4d\u0d31 ","option4":"\u0d21\u0d4b. \u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d. \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d7b","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"45","question":"\u0d38\u0d48\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d32\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d48\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \ufffd\ufffd\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33 \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d","option1":"\u0d07\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d3f","option2":"\u0d05\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d40\u0d7b \u0d16\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d1c\u0d3f","option3":"\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d37\u0d3e \u0d24\u0d41\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d ","option4":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d40\u0d7b \u0d10\u0d2c\u0d15\u0d4d ","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"46","question":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d40\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d41\u0d31\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02?","option1":"\u0d2a\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d2e \u0d2c\u0d02\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d7e","option2":"\u0d17\u0d41\u0d1c\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d","option3":"\u0d12\u0d31\u0d40\u0d38 ","option4":"\u0d06\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"47","question":"\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3e \u0d32\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d30\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d23\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d34\u0d4d\u200c\u0d38\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d15\u0d35\u0d30\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f?","option1":"\u0d2d\u0d17\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d","option2":"\u0d38\u0d41\u0d16\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d47\u0d35\u0d4d ","option3":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41","option4":"\u0d38\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d46\u0d7b","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"48","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \ufffd\ufffd\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d7b \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d09\u0d7e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d?","option1":" \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d02","option2":"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d31\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b\u0d21\u0d7d \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d02","option3":"\u0d17\u0d41\u0d1c\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d02","option4":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7a \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d02","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"49","question":"\u0d06\u0d38\u0d42\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d23 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d37\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?","option1":"\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d1c\u0d28 \u0d2d\u0d35\u0d7b","option2":"\u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37 \u0d2d\u0d35\u0d7b","option3":" \u0d06\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26 \u0d2d\u0d35\u0d7b","option4":"\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d26\u0d7b ","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"50","question":"\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d7c\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d35\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d15\u0d46. \u0d15\u0d47\u0d33\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7b ","option2":"\u0d35\u0d3f.\u0d2a\u0d3f. \u0d2e\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d7b ","option3":"\u0d0e.\u0d15\u0d46. \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33","option4":"\u0d1f\u0d3f.\u0d15\u0d46. \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d35\u0d7b ","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"51","question":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d46\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d2e\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d42\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d23\u0d02?","option1":"48 \u0d2e\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d42\u0d7c","option2":"24 \u0d2e\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d42\u0d7c","option3":"36 \u0d2e\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d42\u0d7c","option4":"12 \u0d2e\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d42\u0d7c","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"52","question":"\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2c\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d38 \u0d38\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d7c \u0d24\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d34\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d41\u0d19\u0d4d \u0d39\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2d\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d?","option1":"\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d28","option2":"\u0d17\u0d02\u0d17","option3":"\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d41","option4":"\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"53","question":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d7a\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d23\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d33\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?","option1":"\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d46","option2":"\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d7c","option3":"\u0d2c\u0d02\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d7e","option4":"\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u200c\u0d28\u0d57","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"54","question":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d15\u0d24, \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02, \u0d38\u0d41\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37 \u0d07\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d48\u0d2c\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d47\u0d24\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d02?","option1":"\u0d38\u0d48\u0d2c\u0d7c \u0d1f\u0d46\u0d31\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d02","option2":"\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d","option3":"\u0d38\u0d48\u0d2c\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d4d\u200c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d","option4":"\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"55","question":"\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d24\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d12\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d35\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d?","option1":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15","option2":"\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2f\u0d42\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d7b","option3":"\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7b","option4":"\u0d1c\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7b","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"56","question":"1959 \u0d7d \u0d1c\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d47\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d38\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d07\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d32 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?","option1":"\u0d31\u0d42\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d32","option2":"\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d4d","option3":"\u0d1c\u0d02\u0d37\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d7c","option4":"\u0d26\u0d41\u0d7c\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d7c","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"57","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d46\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d?","option1":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f","option2":"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d ","option3":"\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7d ","option4":"\u0d35\u0d47\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"58","question":"1930 \u0d32\u0d46 \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d38\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d47\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02?","option1":"\u0d35\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d30 ","option2":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f","option3":"\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d42\u0d7c","option4":"\u0d06\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d42\u0d7c","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"59","question":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d24\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d4d\u200c\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d35\u0d47\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d23\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d42\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d? ","option1":"1961","option2":"1955","option3":"1959","option4":"1965","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"60","question":"\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d42\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d24\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?","option1":"\u0d21\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d","option2":"\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d","option3":"\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d7b","option4":"\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d17\u0d40\u0d38\u0d4d","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"61","question":"\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d41\u0d17\u0d24\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d?","option1":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d34","option2":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d3f ","option3":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3e \u0d2a\u0d42\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7e","option4":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d35\u0d39\u0d43\u0d26\u0d2f\u0d02","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"62","question":"\u0d05\u0d28\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7b \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d05\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d7b","option2":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7b","option3":"\u0d05\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1b\u0d7b","option4":"\u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d41 ","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"63","question":"\u0d24\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d02?","option1":"3","option2":"2","option3":"4","option4":"5","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"64","question":"\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d42\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?","option1":" \u0d2a\u0d3f.\u0d38\u0d3f. \u0d15\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d7b","option2":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f \r\n","option3":"\u0d2a\u0d3f.\u0d38\u0d3f. \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d7b","option4":"\u0d0e.\u0d15\u0d46. \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d7b","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"65","question":"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d36\u0d48\u0d32\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d?","option1":"\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d46\u0d31\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d35\u0d7b","option2":"\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d31\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2d\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ","option3":"\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2d\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ","option4":"\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d31\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2d\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"66","question":"\u0d35\u0d46\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7b \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d13\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d","option2":"\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d7d \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d","option3":"\u0d05\u0d38\u0d41\u0d30\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ","option4":"\u0d0f\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"67","question":"'Where there is life there is hope' \u0d08 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d24\u0d7c\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d2e \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d?","option1":"\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d15\u0d7e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 ","option2":"\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d28\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d ","option3":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d07\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d02","option4":"\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d3f","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"68","question":"\u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2e\u0d3e \u0d24\u0d7d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d30\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d?","option1":"\u0d38\u0d41\u0d16\u0d26\u0d41\u0d03\u0d16\u0d02 ","option2":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d15\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d02","option3":"\u0d24\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d28\u0d3f","option4":"\u0d28\u0d40\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d18\u0d02","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"69","question":"'John prefers English novels to Malayalam ones' \u0d08 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d24\u0d7c\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d2e \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d?","option1":"\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d32\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d32\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d","option2":"\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d32\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7e \u0d07\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d32\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02","option3":"\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d32\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d32\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ","option4":"\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d40\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d32\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"70","question":"\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d05\u0d35\u0d7b \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41. \u0d08 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d46\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d?","option1":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d15\u0d7e","option2":"\u0d05\u0d35\u0d7b","option3":"\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3e\u0d2f ","option4":"\u0d05\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"71","question":"Mr. Manoj ........... the work in November last year","option1":"Start","option2":"Started","option3":"will start","option4":"have started","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"72","question":"Find the exact word which means that happens now and then","option1":"occasional","option2":"frequent","option3":"often","option4":"gradual","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"73","question":"An article is wrongly used here. Find the word:","option1":"a flower","option2":"an African","option3":"a furniture","option4":"the ganges","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"74","question":"His actions are","option1":"destroyer","option2":"destruction","option3":"destructive","option4":"destroyed","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"75","question":"He is jealous...... his friend's success","option1":"with","option2":"on","option3":"of","option4":"by","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"76","question":"They went to a film,..........","option1":"did they?","option2":"didn't they?","option3":"do they?","option4":"haven't they?","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"77","question":"When I reached the station, the train:","option1":"had left","option2":"have left","option3":"left","option4":"will leave","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"78","question":"Antonym of 'accept'","option1":"refuse","option2":"rebuke","option3":"receive","option4":"reject","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"79","question":"Synonym of 'Cautious'","option1":"beware","option2":"careful","option3":"casual","option4":"calm","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"80","question":"Plural of 'Knife'","option1":"Knives","option2":"Knifes","option3":"Knifs","option4":"Knivfes","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"81","question":"Which is the .......... city in India?","option1":"big","option2":"biggest","option3":"bigger","option4":"most biggest","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"82","question":"John and his brother ............ hard","option1":"working","option2":"will be work","option3":"work","option4":"works","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"83","question":"All the milk ............sour","option1":"was","option2":"were","option3":"are","option4":"has","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"84","question":"Add a prefix to get the opposite meaning of the word 'able'","option1":"disable","option2":"inable","option3":"unable","option4":"misable","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"85","question":"The word 'martial' means","option1":"of marriage","option2":"relating to war","option3":"upholding law","option4":"rule or docrine","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"86","question":"Plural of 'manservant'","option1":"manservants","option2":"menservants","option3":"menservant","option4":"mensservants","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"87","question":"Select an uncountable noun from the following:","option1":"pin","option2":"poem","option3":"train","option4":"poetry","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"88","question":"Which of the following words are wrongly paired?","option1":"Hunter-Huntress","option2":"Bridegroom-Bride","option3":"Sultan-Sultana","option4":"Bull-Belly","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"89","question":"Thieves broke into her house here the phrase broke intomeans","option1":"begin suddenly ","option2":"enter by force","option3":"collapse","option4":"split into parts","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"90","question":"Panorama has the meaning","option1":"wild and noisy disorder","option2":"wide sight without interruption","option3":"whatever happens by chance","option4":"what cannot be understood","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"91","question":"\u0d06\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d?","option1":"\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d7c","option2":"\u0d1c\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d17\u0d40\u0d7c","option3":"\u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d7c","option4":"\u0d14\u0d31\u0d02\u0d17\u0d38\u0d40\u0d2c\u0d4d","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"92","question":"\u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4a\u0d34\u0d41\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d0f\u0d15 \u0d39\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d?","option1":"\u0d05\u0d33\u0d15\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26","option2":"\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d41","option3":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f ","option4":"\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d28","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"93","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d28\u0d02\u0d35\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41? ","option1":"\u0d35\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d ","option2":"\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d","option3":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d","option4":"\u0d07\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f ","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"94","question":"\u0d35\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d42\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d30\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d?","option1":"\u0d2c\u0d46\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2c\u0d46\u0d31\u0d3f","option2":"\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c","option3":" \u0d15\u0d23","option4":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d02","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"95","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d3e \u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d32\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d02?","option1":"14","option2":"28","option3":"20","option4":"25","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"96","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d17\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d2a\u0d40\u0d21\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d23 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d ?","option1":"2005","option2":"2004","option3":"2006","option4":"2000","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"97","question":"\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d31\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e?","option1":"\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d28\u0d57\u0d15","option2":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d47\u0d39\u0d38\u0d40\u0d2e \r\n","option3":"\u0d24\u0d41\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02","option4":"\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"98","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d34\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d02\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30?\r\n","option1":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d2f","option2":"\u0d06\u0d30\u0d35\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f ","option3":"\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02","option4":"\u0d2a\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"99","question":"\u0d38\u0d48\u0d32\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41? ","option1":"\u0d07\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f","option2":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d","option3":"\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d","option4":"\u0d24\u0d43\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d36\u0d42\u0d7c","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"100","question":"\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d30 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d16\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2b\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02","option2":"\u0d09\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d38\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d02","option3":"\u0d2c\u0d02\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d7e \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2d\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d02","option4":"\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02","answer":"3"}]
}
}
